乔西
Josie?
天啊  你吓死我了
God, you scared me.
抱歉  我只是想确定你没事
I'm sorry, I just wanted to make sure that you were okay.
为什么
Why?
我不知道
I don't know.
我只是一直在想着你
I guess I've just been thinking about you.
是吗
You have?
实际上  我控制不住自己一直在想你
Actually, I can't stop thinking about you.
我也一直在想你
I've been thinking about you, too.
已经过了宵禁时间了
It's past curfew.
爸爸会很生气的
And Dad's gonna be so pissed.
你做春梦了
You were having a sex dream.
什么  没有  我没做
What? No, I wasn't.
别跟我说你梦见兰登了
Please tell me it wasn't Landon.
或者说
Or Hope,
是霍普
for that matter.
我没做春梦
I wasn't having a sex dream.
赶紧睡吧
Go back to sleep.
第2季   第14集
吸血鬼后裔
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
作为超自然存在
As supernaturals,
我们都背负着包袱
we all carry a burden.
我们都警惕着邪恶的人
Our eyes are open to evil.
但最近  必须得面对他们
And recently,  you've had to face it.
翻 译  Lysenko
我们中有人通过否认事实
Some of us process these traumas
来处理这些精神创伤
by suppressing what happened.
翻 译  小菲
对于其他人  假装什么事情都没发生过
For others, it's easier  to bury it deep inside
把感觉深藏似乎更容易一些
and pretend like  nothing's happened at all.
然而  还有些人用了不一样的方法  比如
Still, others may take a different route, such as...
翻 译  岛岛
排斥他人  自我封闭
Pushing people away in an attempt to self-isolate?
翻 译  小螺号
因为他们深爱的所有人都不断处于危险中
Because everyone they love is in perpetual danger,
很多人也永远的离开了我们
which often results in them becoming perpetually dead.
看到了吗  就这个
See? There.
这就是我的治疗方案
That's it. That's my therapy.
我能走了吗  因为兰登正在外面想尝试飞行
Can I go now? Because, uh, Landon's outside trying to fly
需要个观测手  恐怕不行  霍普
and could use a spotter. I'm afraid not, Hope,
特效：小螺号
重点是我们都能更好的处理
because the point is we can all do better
那些经历带来的精神创伤
at processing the traumas we've been through.
所以萨尔茨曼博士今天
Which is why Dr. Saltzman has asked me to conduct
校 对   小狐狸
让我组织一场特殊的小组课程
a special group lesson today.
就拿我来说  我真的需要这个
I, for one, could really use this,
特 效   麦 斯
我会很感激所有人的支持的
and I would appreciate everyone's support.
说实话  我不知道
Honestly, I don't know
我为什么来这儿  不过我愿意提供帮助
why I'm here, but I'm down to help.
你们都会
You will all
在这次模拟中扮演重要的角色
have an important role to play in this simulation.
别那么看着我了
Oh, stop looking at me like that.
会很好玩的
It'll be fun.
这个设备
This device
是鲁伯特·瓦尔德穆斯教授发明的
was created by Professor Rupert Vardemus.
好吧
Okay...
真正的瓦尔德穆斯教授
The real Professor Vardemus.
他在神秘治疗学圈子里很出名
He's quite famous in mystical therapeutic circles.
这是他做的不同版本的狩猎室
It's his variation on a Chambre de Chasse.
你们心里关注的所有问题都会传输到里面
All your psychological concerns will be transferred inside
形成共享的故事
to form a shared narrative.
你们一起创造出的世界什么样子都有可能
Now, the world you create together can be anything,
可能是海盗也可能是冷战间谍
from pirates on the high seas to spies in the Cold War.
但不管最后看起来是什么样子
But no matter what it ends up looking like,
都是专门用来帮助你的
it will be designed specifically to help you.
在这里  你是无意识的
Out here, you're unconscious.
你不会发现你是在模拟中
You'll have no awareness that you're in a simulation.
是像游戏一样吗
So, it's like a game?
- 我怎么才能赢呢  - 只需要
- Uh, how do I win? - Simply reach
到达故事的结尾  你就会得到逃脱关键词
the end of your story and you'll be given an escape word.
说出那个词  你的意识就会回归
Say it aloud and you'll become self-aware again,
然后醒过来
then wake up here,
在这个过程中你会获得非常有价值的体会
having discovered something valuable in the process.
- 还有问题吗  - 是的
- Any questions? - Uh, yeah.
我有个问题  她来这儿干什么
I have a question. What the hell is she doing here?
嗨  不好意思我迟到了
Hi. Uh, sorry I'm late.
做了很奇怪的梦
Uh, weird dreams.
你来的刚好  洁德
You're just in time, Jade.
别担心
Don't worry.
我们在这儿要做的就是个模拟而已
What we're about to do here is merely a simulation.
我也会在里面
And I'll be in it as well,
并且全程都意识清醒
and self-aware the whole time.
我保证会仔细观察你们每个人的
I promise to keep a careful eye on all of you.
所有人都开始想象
Everyone think
阳光明媚色彩鲜艳的热带海滩
of bright, sunny, tropical beaches.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
空气像亲吻尸体的感觉一样冰凉
The air was as cold  as a kiss from a corpse.
我的伴侣晚上工作  所以现在我也是
My partner worked at night,  and now, so did I.
我要是想找到他  就必须这样做
I had to, if I was  ever going to find him.
不过往好处看  至少我知道从哪里开始找
But on the bright side, at least I knew where to start.
因为在神秘瀑布镇的所有人都知道一件事
Because there's one thing that everyone in Mystic Falls knows.
兰登酒吧
所有丢失了的东西都会去一个地方
There's a place  where the lost things go.
谢谢
* Thanks *
那些回忆
* For the memory *
海滩上灼伤的皮肤
* Of sunburns at the shore *
在新加坡的夜晚
* Nights in Singapore *
你曾经让我头疼
* You might have been a headache *
但从来没让我讨厌
* But you never were a bore *
所以谢谢你
* So thank you *
非常感谢
* So much... *
那个摄影师
That photographer.
他从机场就跟着我们
He followed us from the airport.
我就是来抛头露面的  乔
I'm in town to make a picture, Jo.
越多曝光率越好
The more publicity, the better.
作为你姐姐  更重要的是
As your sister, but more importantly,
作为你的公关  我不同意
your publicist, I disagree.
我们需要掌控人设
We need to control the narrative.
因为如果你从那个角度看着还算漂亮的话
Because if you still looked good from that angle,
霍华德·霍克斯:著名导演
我们就会跟霍华德·霍克斯合作了
we'd be working with Howard Hawks.
好吧
Fine.
那至少等你把他吓跑之后
Then at least find me another drink
再给我拿杯喝的来
after you're done scaring him off.
好像你还需要喝一杯似的
As if you need another drink.
高呼万岁
* Hooray for us *
多谢那些回忆
* And thanks for the memory *
那么多小小的梦想
* And how are all the little dreams *
怎么从来不能成真
* That never did come true? *
谢谢你
* So thank you *
非常感谢
* So much. *
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
我是艾玛·提格
I'm Emma Tig.
我要休息一会儿  不过别担心
I'll be taking a break, but don't worry,
如果有人需要我  我今天晚上都在这儿
I'll be here all night, if anyone needs my help.
这可不是什么窥视秀
This ain't a peep show.
你能怪我吗
Can you blame me?
伊丽莎白·萨尔茨曼是明星  我看过她所有的电影
Elizabeth Saltzman's a star. I've seen all of her movies.
我真的是脸盲
I'm bad with faces.
我希望不是这么回事
I'm hoping that's not the case.
我在找我老板
I'm looking for my boss,
这个镇上最好的私人侦探
the best P.I. this town's ever known.
我说过  我是脸盲
Like I said, I'm bad with faces.
他现在很危险  迈克尔森小姐
He's in danger, Miss Mikaelson.
你怎么知道我叫什么
How do you know my name?
我还知道你的售酒执照过期了
The same way I know your liquor license is expired.
所以
So,
咱们互相帮个忙吧
let's help each other out.
他看上去像是会来这里听音乐的男人
He looks like the kind of guy who comes here for the music.
我要是你的话
If I were you,
就去问问唱歌的那个人  我是不会去的
I'd ask the dame who sings, because I don't.
提格小姐
Miss Tig?
我能问你个
I'd like to have a quick...
问题吗
word.
瓦尔德穆斯
Vardemus.
我叫福尔摩斯  小伙子
My name is Holmes, dear boy.
夏洛克·福尔摩斯
Sherlock Holmes.
这怎么可能
How is this possible?
早上好
Good morning.
你酒醒了吗
You sobered up yet?
我很少喝酒
I rarely drink.
只是偶尔喝点啤酒什么的
The occasional seven percent solution, perhaps.
你酗酒成性  鲁伯特
You're an alcoholic, Rupert.
我们是合伙人  朋友
We're partners. Friends.
所以你给我买了袖扣吗
That explains the cufflinks you bought for me.
我再说最后一次
For the last time!
我的搭档叫华生  我叫
My partner's name is Watson and mine is...
夏洛克·福尔摩斯
Sherlock Holmes.
我知道
I know.
不过我到底是怎么到这儿来的  我也很糊涂
Though how I ended up here confounds even me.
今天早上我一醒来  就发现身边的一切都不一样了
I woke this morning and the world around me had changed.
不过虽然周围的环境不一样了  可我还记得
But though my surroundings were different, I remembered
正在调查的一个案子
the case I was working on.
我正在找的是  蓝宝石
What I was looking for: the Blue Carbuncle,
一种罕见珍贵的宝石
a rare and precious gemstone,
从莫卡伯爵夫人那里被偷走了
stolen from the countess of Morcar.
所以你能想象的到我有多吃惊
So you can imagine my surprise when it turned up
居然在这个沉闷世界的报纸广告上
in a newspaper advertisement for this dreary world,
看到宝石戴在酒吧歌手的脖子上
around the neck of a lounge singer.
是死了的酒吧歌手  你的指纹到处都是
A dead lounge singer, with your fingerprints all over her.
我深表怀疑
I doubt that very much,
你也应该怀疑  因为我带着手套呢
as should you, given I was wearing gloves.
你推理出她是死于
Have you deduced
氰化物中毒吗
that she died of cyanide poisoning yet?
香槟吗
The champagne?
显然易见
It's elementary.
她指甲下面的皮肤已经变成玫瑰色了
The skin beneath her fingernails had turned the color of roses.
这是她的细胞无法获得
A direct result of her cells being unable to absorb
血液中的氧气造成的直接结果
the oxygen that remained in her blood.
找到是谁给酒瓶里投的毒
Find who poisoned the bottle...
就能找到凶手了
...and you'll have found your killer.
我是助手
I'm the sidekick.
你是负责动脑的  所以我需要你帮助
You are the brains, which is why I need your help
把这个查清楚  抱歉  老兄
to get to the bottom of this. Sorry, old chap.
我还有自己的迷需要解开
I have my own mystery to solve.
詹姆斯·瑞德偷了宝石
James Ryder stole the jewel.
酒店服务员
The hotel attendant?
大胆的猜测  你怎么想到的
A bold theory. How did you arrive at it?
我没有  是你想到的
I didn't. You did.
《福尔摩斯侦探集》
好好读读  希望等我回来的时候
So read up, and hopefully by the time I'm back,
你就是我认识的那个人了
you'll be the man I know again.
新氧
医美
●
新氧视频面诊
医生好不好 当面聊 才知道
医美|皮肤科|齿科|眼科|植发
你怎么进来的
How did you get in?
门没锁
The door was unlocked.
你真不会撒谎
You're a terrible liar.
我也不擅长当侦探
I'm a terrible detective, too.
不过撬锁的本事还可以
But not half bad at picking locks.
到时候我首先就得跟警察说说这个
Then that'll be the first thing I tell the cops.
还是应该从那个歌手死之前
Or should I start with you going to talk to that singer
你正想去和她谈话开始
right before she died?
他们反正也不在乎
Not like they'd care anyway.
威士忌
Whiskey.
要好的那种  不要劣等货
Preferably the good stuff. Not that rotgut.
我把好酒放后面了
I keep it in the back.
整瓶香槟  送给丽兹·萨尔兹曼
停机
Cut!
我想再拍一条
I'd like to try one more.
你现在才想努力了吗  鲍勃
Oh, you want to start trying now, Bob?
我回车上去了
I'll be in my trailer.
真是  垃圾
That was... Trash.
跟这个愚蠢的恐怖电影一样
Like the rest of this stupid horror flick.
我被一个男人鱼给杀了
I get murdered by a mer-man.
男人鱼  开什么玩笑  没人会看这种垃圾
A mer-man! Honestly, no one's gonna watch this crap.
别挡路  贱人们
Ooh. Out of my way, you trollops.
我的酒壶呢
Where is my flask?
别管酒壶了  记者又回来了
Never mind that, he's back.
我看上去怎么样
How do I look?
不重要  反正这些照片
Doesn't matter, 'cause these photos are never
不会公开的
seeing the light of day.
你很漂亮  萨尔茨曼小姐
You look beautiful, Miss Saltzman.
我能问你几个问题吗
Can I ask you a few questions?
你是记者么
You a reporter?
也不是
Not exactly.
不过我确实做一些报道的工作
But I do have something to report.
有人想杀了你
Someone's trying to kill you.
香烟也会杀人的
Cigarettes kill people, too.
我这辈子是绝对不会抽烟的
I'd never smoked  a day in my life,
不过那个时候  我理解你有那种冲动
but in that moment,  I understood the urge
虽然知道对你不好  但是就想来一支的感觉
to put your lips on something  you knew was bad for you.
谢谢  抱歉
Thank you. I'm sorry.
我还有点害怕
I'm still a little shaken up.
很能理解
That's understandable.
就像我说的  下了毒的香槟昨晚本来是
As I was saying, poisoned champagne was sent
要送到你的桌上的
to your table last night.
幸运的是  被别人喝掉了
Lucky for you, it ended up on the wrong lips.
你知道会有谁想让你死吗
Any idea who would want you dead?
没有人  我只是个过气的演员
None. I'm just a washed-up actress.
我想象不到有谁会在意我到
I can't imagine anyone caring enough about me
给我送香槟  更别说杀我了
to send champagne, much less kill me.
拜托你  格莱斯利
Please, Mr. Greasley,
尽管我的人生很糟糕  但是我不想死
as messed up as my life is, I don't want to die.
你不会死
You won't.
我保证  我的搭档是个天才
I promise. My partner's a genius.
他会破了这个案子
He'll crack this case, and...
不论如何  我不认为
For what it's worth, I don't think
你过气  萨尔茨曼女士
you're washed up, Miss Saltzman.
拜托  请叫我
Please, call me...
丽兹
Lizzie.
我弄清楚那个摄影师为谁工作了
I found out who that photographer works for.
你是什么人
And who the hell are you?
只是仰慕者
Just a fan.
这没想到
Well, I'll be damned.
就是酒店服务生
It was the hotel attendant.
明神醒智
"Liquet."
所示章节出自亚瑟·柯南·道尔勋爵所著《红桦庄探案 (The Adventure of the Copper Beeches)》
那是我游戏的结束
That was the end of my game.
我不是夏洛克·福尔摩斯
I'm not Sherlock Holmes.
我是鲁伯特·瓦尔德穆斯
I'm Rupert Vardemus.
我不是侦探  我是教授
And I'm not a detective, I'm a professor.
是你吗  米尔顿
Is that you, Milton?
我知道这一定很让人困惑
I know this must be all very confusing.
我在学校档案上见过你的名字
I remember your name from the school dossiers.
我记起来了所有事
I remember everything.
事实上  多亏了
In fact, thanks to--
你
You!
这说不通
This doesn't make any sense.
他们其中应该有人醒来了
One of them should be awake by now.
闩锁顿开
Dissero.
瓦尔德穆斯教授
Professor Vardemus.
怎么回事
How?
那个混蛋克拉克把我的身体锁在了这里
That pustule Clarke locked my body in here.
在这之前他把我的神智锁在了那个盒子里
But not before he locked my mind away in that box.
你也进入了游戏
Wait, you were in the game, too.
我是被你们的学生之一谋杀的
I was murdered by one of your students.
和你一样
Like you.
就这么定了
Then that settles it.
我们必须终止模拟
We have to end the simulation.
你这么做对他们弊大于利
You'd be doing them more harm than good.
他们所经历的只仅仅是
While what they're experiencing is merely
他们思想的呈现
a manifestation of their minds,
而涉及谋杀的念头不是小事
a narrative involving murder is still a serious matter.
这指向了游戏中的
It points to someone inside the game
某个人正处于精神崩溃的边缘
being on the verge of a psychological break.
现在终止  可能会加重症状
Terminate the session now, and you may cement that fracture.
那我们该怎么做
So what are we supposed to do?
做出最困难的决定
The hardest thing of all.
相信他们在没有我们干预的情况下解决问题
Trust them to resolve the issue without us.
你知道是谁杀的你吗
Do you know who killed you?
乔西
萨尔瓦托  酒店
像你这样的贵妇在
Well, well, what's a classy broad like you
这种地方做什么
doing in this gin joint?
被勒索  着你已经知道了  洁德
Being blackmailed, but you already knew that, Jade.
所以有话直说  为了我姐妹的照片
So cut to the chase and name your price
你想要多少钱
for those photos of my sister.
这不是前的问题
This isn't about money.
这是我职业生涯中挖到的最精彩的报道
It's about the best story of my career.
人气不再的女影星接不到片约
A fading starlet can't get hired in the movies anymore.
幸运的是
But lucky for her,
她有一个双胞胎姐妹放弃了一切
she's got a twin sister who left everything behind
来做她的公关
to become her publicist.
而她很清楚怎么样才能让她重回聚光灯下
One that knows exactly how to get her back into the spotlight.
即使这意味着让她成为谋杀的目标
Even if it means making her the target of a murderer.
我分析的怎么样
How am I doing so far?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
姐妹/公关对记者如是说
Said the sister/publicist to the reporter.
但是她遗漏了一个重要的事实
But she was missing an important fact.
记者知道她的破绽
The reporter knew her tell.
她在撒谎的时候会下意识
She had a habit of picking off her nail polish
抠指甲
when she was lying.
你怎么知道的
How did you know?
我费了些功夫
I figured it out the hard way.
你那晚愤然离开时候在抠指甲
You were picking at your nails the night you walked out on me,
嘴上说你会回来的
saying you'd be back.
- 我不是那个意思  - 我知道
- That isn't what I meant. - I know.
我收买了俱乐部的侍者
I bribed a waiter at the club,
他说是你买了那瓶
and he told me that you were the one
杀死死者的香槟
that bought that champagne that killed that singer.
用的是氰化物
Cyanide poisoning.
- 我还买通了验尸官  - 那是个意外
- I bribed the coroner as well. - It was an accident.
丽兹本该被送进医院
Lizzie was supposed to be rushed to the hospital
然后借此为她的新电影造势
to get some press for her movie.
我没有给任何人下毒
I didn't use enough poison to kill anyone.
我都不知道那个歌手拿到了香槟
I don't even know how that singer got that bottle.
现在最重要的是她已经死了
All that matters is that she's dead.
只有把你关进监狱
And putting you behind bars is the only way
才能让你摆脱你姐妹的魔爪
I'll ever pry you out of your sister's claws.
等等
Wait.
最后再和我喝一杯
Have one last drink with me.
为了旧日的情分
for old time's sake.
太迟了  乔西
Too late, Jose.
也许是因为我喝醉了
Maybe it's the booze talking,
但这是最后一次和你见面
but I just had to see you one last time.
失陪
Excuse me.
乔塞特·萨尔茨曼
Josette Saltzman.
我想我们都知道
I think we both know there's no need
没必要再检查脉搏了
to check her for a pulse.
相信我  我有自知之明
Trust me, I am totally  self-aware.
我用不着你的游戏告诉我
I didn't need your stupid game
我对乔西萨尔茨曼有好感
to tell me I have the hots for Josie Saltzman.
好吗  我在监狱世界见到她就知道了
All right? I've known that since I saw her in the prison world.
如果洁德被提早从模拟中弹出
If Jade was ejected from the simulation prematurely,
这意味着规则改变了
it means the rules have changed.
有人在重写规则
Someone's rewriting them
从游戏内部
from inside the game itself.
怎么做到的  是谁在做
How? Who?
一个能够使用强大的法术
Someone with access to very powerful magic...
而且需要除掉碍事的人
who needs everyone out of the way
好达成自己的目的
so they can get whatever it is they want.
简而言之
In short,
就是杀死我们的人
the person who killed us all.
我们应该问的问题是
So, the question we should be asking ourselves is...
凶手为什么这么做
...why they did it.
我听说那个记者的事了
I heard about your reporter.
警察弄清楚是谁杀的她了吗
The cops know who killed her?
杀死你们的歌手的同一个人
Same person who murdered your singer.
但是我不认为她们在乎
But I don't think they're too interested in
弄清楚凶手是谁
figuring out who that is.
真希望我能够为她多做些什么
Wish I could have done more for her.
那晚拍照的时候你在现场
You were in here that night taking photos.
你想要帮忙吗
You want to help?
把胶卷洗出来仔细检查一下你看到了什么
Develop that film and take a hard look at whatever you see.
对不起  这不关我的事
Sorry. It's none of my business.
我还和兰登有联系啊
I still talk to Landon, you know.
- 他怎么样  - 他没事
- How is he? - He's good.
他很享受升职去加州的生活
Promotion in California is going good for him.
但是他还是想念你  霍普
But he still misses you, Hope.
是他要离开的
He's the one who left.
因为你不肯和他走
Because you didn't go with him.
一通电话就能重归于好
But you can change that with a phone call.
他可以给你买明天的巴士票
He'd buy you a bus ticket tomorrow.
我会自己买票
I can buy my own ticket.
你可以把那些照片洗出来
And you can develop those photos.
你确定你没有什么要说的了
You sure you don't have  anything else to say?
认罪中通常包括你犯罪的原因
Confessions usually include why you did the crime.
这还重要吗
Does it matter?
当然重要
Of course it does.
你签了名之后
You sign that line and the next chair you'll be sitting in
你就会坐上电椅
is gonna plug into the wall.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
往好处想
Look on the bright side.
在我被处刑的时候你会受到嘉奖
They'll give you a medal when I ride the lightning.
嘉奖是给英雄的
Medals are for heroes.
我只不过是想要弄清楚是谁毒害了他的搭档
I'm just a guy trying to figure out who poisoned his partner.
我已经告诉你了  是我
I already told you, it was me.
我毒害了你的搭档
I poisoned your partner
还有那个歌手
and that singer
还有洁德
and Jade.
带我去警局吧
Now take me down to the station.
我不能这么做
I can't do that.
为什么不能能
And why the hell not?
因为我的搭档是被枪杀的
Because my partner was shot.
你没有杀任何人  乔塞特
You didn't kill anyone, Josette.
但是只可能是我
But it had to be me.
线索说不通
The pieces don't fit.
你为什么要背黑锅
So why are you trying to make them?
因为如果不是我  就是丽兹
Because if it wasn't me, it was Lizzie.
如果我们其中一个要死  我宁愿是我
And if one of us has to die, I'd rather it be me.
你看到了吗
Do you see that?
护身庇体
"Praesidio."
- MG - 我想要 告诉她
- MG. -I wanted to tell her
我在那张纸上看到了什么
that I saw something  on that piece of paper,
但是就像 他们所说
but it's like they say...
死无对证
...dead men tell no tales.
别这么做  我不许你这么做
Don't do this. I won't let you.
我一向认为你是个了不起的演员
Always thought you were a hell of an actress...
是你吗  鲍勃
Is that you, Bob?
我的合约中写的很清楚
My contract explicitly says
拍摄结束我就不用和你交谈了
that I don't have to talk to you after we wrap.
但是神秘的凶手将是你的最后一个角色
...but being the Mystic Mauler is going to be your last role.
你在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
别演了  你威慑呢要这么做
Drop the act. Why'd you do it?
做什么
Do what?
杀害那些人  就从你的姐妹说起
Murder all those people. Maybe start with your sister.
乔西死了
Josie's dead?
我本来也会死  但是幸运的是  我的口袋里装着这个
I should be, too. But lucky me, I had this in my pocket.
这是你的酒壶  不是吗
It's your flask, right?
你用来毒害那个歌手的酒壶
The one you poisoned the singer with,
这一系列事件的开始
the one that started this whole mess?
如我所言  你是个了不起的演员
Like I said, you're a hell of an actress.
所以那些鳄鱼的眼泪不会阻止我把你抓捕归案
So those crocodile tears won't stop me from bringing you in.
这一次 我不在乎我自己
For once, I don't care about myself.
我没有做你所说的那些事  但是
I didn't do what you said, but...
但是我难辞其咎  因为我只在乎我自己
I may as well have, because I was so wrapped up in myself
却没有意识到自己的姐妹陷入了危险
that I didn't know my sister was in danger.
我没能救她
I wasn't there to save her.
一叶障目
"Caecus."
谢天谢地
Thank God.
这是我的逃脱词
Oh, that's my escape word.
这意味着这一切都不是真的
Which means none of this is real,
乔西还活着我总算可以离开这个愚蠢的游戏了
Josie's still alive and I can finally leave this stupid game.
艾玛  我准备好了
Okay, Emma. I'm ready.
拉我出去
Yank me out.
不管用什么咒语
Abracadabra or whatever.
该死  为什么不管用
Son of a bitch. Why isn't it working?
你精神崩溃了  萨尔茨曼女士
You're cracking up, Miss Saltzman.
不许再说我是疯子
Don't you label me insane again, okay?
我是一个头脑清醒的人
I am the only person here who is in their right mind.
我们只需要找到你的逃离词
We just need to find you your escape word.
有话留给法官说吧
Save it for the judge.
那好  MG
Oh. Yeah, that's-that's good, MG.
我叫米尔顿
My name's Milton.
我知道
I know, okay?
我很了解你  米尔顿·格莱斯利
I know you as well as anyone, Milton Greasley.
虽说这一点让我有点不好意思
Look, I'm not proud of this,
但是我算是你的弱点
but I'm kind of, like, your blind spot.
你迷恋我的程度让你对我言听计从
You are so into me that you'll sort of do whatever I say,
给我戴上手铐也许
so slap those puppies on me and maybe
你就能清醒过来
you'll get over your block.
新氧
医美
●
新氧视频面诊
医生好不好 当面聊 才知道
医美|皮肤科|齿科|眼科|植发
或者我们可以一起私奔
Or we could run away together.
去真正的海滩
Maybe to a real beach.
去墨西哥
Mexico.
警察永远别想找到我们
:The cops will never find us.
你是认真的吗
Is this a serious offer?
当然不是  你确信我是凶手
Hell no. But the fact that you're convinced I'm a killer
还考虑和我私奔证明了我的观点
and you still considered it totally proves my point.
快给我拷上
Now Fifty Shades me.
英  雄
英雄
"Heros."
丽兹
Lizzie.
我记起来了
I remember.
我们为什么还被困在这
Then why are we still trapped here?
这太让人抓狂了
This is maddening.
快给我拿下来
Get these stupid cuffs off me.
这个游戏出了问题
There's something wrong with the game.
丽兹  快跑
Lizzie, run.
找到霍普
Find Hope.
糟糕
Oh, crap.
迪格女士
Ms. Tig.
丽兹  她刚刚说了逃离词  但她
Lizzie, she-she got her escape word, but she's still
还在游戏中
in the game.
而且
And...
乔西死了
...Josie died.
我看到了  所以为什么她还在里面
I saw it. So why is she still in there?
我们不营业
We're closed.
霍普·安德里亚·麦克尔森
Hope Andrea Mikaelson!
给我开门
Open this damn door!
有人要杀我
Someone's trying to kill me!
你是那个电影明星啊
You're that movie star.
- 你怎么知道我叫什么  - 说来话长
- How do you know my name? - It's a long story.
你不会信的
Which you won't believe.
但我可以证明
But, um, oh, I can prove it.
我知道你不为人知的心伤
I know your deep, dark damage.
你不能跟人太近
You don't get close to people
因为这样  他们要么离开你  要么会死
because they leave you or die, right?
如果你不让我进去
Well, that's exactly what's gonna happen
就会发生这种情况
if you don't let me in.
所以拜托了  帮我就是帮你自己
So, please, help me help you.
你说的没错
You're right.
我一辈子都不停推开别人
I've spent my whole life pushing people away.
现在我要改变了
And I'm about to change that
我要去追随我爱的男人
by going after the man that I love.
抱歉了  我还得赶公车
So, sorry, but I have a bus to catch.
不不不  霍普  霍普
No, no, no. Hope, Hope, Hope, Hope.
死亡
"Mortem."
拉斐尔
Rafael.
没事了
It's okay.
你回来了
You're back.
那里发生什么事
What happened in there?
你又进展了吗
Did you have a breakthrough?
还是那个凶手也把你洗脑了
Or did the killer get to you, too?
不知道
I don't know.
双子农产品
从我家到你家
农场直选  质量保证  送达餐桌
这有点太显而易见了吧
A little on the nose, don't you think?
你好啊  姐妹
Hello, sister.
别那么吃惊嘛
Don't look so shocked.
我们之中走有个人要成为杀手的
One of us was always going to become a killer.
因为融合
Because of the Merge.
一切事情都是因为融合
That's what this whole thing has been about.
是我故意的
I made it that way.
除掉所有人  最后只剩你和我
Remove everyone until it was just you and me.
即便到这时候  乔西还是愿意背锅
Even then, Josie was still willing
让你赢
to take the fall to let you win.
很讽刺吧
Ironic, isn't it?
我为了让乔西活下来  不得不杀了她
I had to kill Josie so that she could survive.
我当然也是她
I am her, too, of course.
她一直埋藏于心的那部分
The parts of her she keeps buried inside.
怨恨你让她那么软弱
That resent her and you for making her weak.
再加上一点黑魔法
Mixed in with a little dark magic.
足够改写规则了
Enough to rewrite the rules
并且让你看看  你永远都比不上我这么强大
and show you that I'm stronger than you can ever be.
我不用玩什么游戏  也知道
I didn't have to play any game to know that.
你一直都这样
You always have been.
所以呢  你现在就要杀了我吗
So what? Are you just gonna kill me now?
你我都清楚  会到今天这一步的
We both knew it would come to this.
好
Fine.
那你赢了
Then you win.
我不玩这什么破模拟游戏了
I'm done with this stupid simulation.
你离不开了
You're not going anywhere.
我该写了规则
I rewrote the rules,
还记得吗
remember?
所以我扳动扳机  你的灵魂就被困在这里
So I pull this trigger, and your mind is stuck here
然后你的身体就等着
while your body waits for me to absorb it
在真实世界的融合中被我吸收吧
during the Merge in the real world.
乔西  不要
Josie, please.
我知道
I-I know I don't do
我没能很好的表现出来
a good job of showing it, but...
但我爱你  比爱自己还爱
I love you, even more than I love myself.
不要杀我
So don't do this.
抱歉  姐妹  不是你死就是我了
Sorry, sis. It's you or me.
你抗争不过命运的
And there's no fighting fate.
你不是要赶公车吗
I thought you had a bus to catch.
我虽然无比想要跟我爱的人在一起
I want to be with the man that I love
比其他任何事都想要
more than I want anything.
但如果有无辜的人要死去
But I couldn't get on that bus
我是不能上那辆车的
if it meant an innocent person had to die.
你这霍普作风太典型了
That is such a Hope move.
你现在看到了一个词对吧
Let me guess. You're seeing a word right now.
对  是什么意思
Yes. What does it mean?
你说出来
Say the word,
我去真实世界里告诉你
and I will tell you in the real world.
命运
Fatum.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
我都开始觉得我自己需要接受心理治疗了
I was beginning to think I'd need therapy myself.
那现在  乔西要怎么办
Now, um... what are we gonna do about Jo?
我这一天已经假装太多了
I've had enough make-believe for one day.
这都是什么
So what the hell is all this?
调研
This is research.
你说乔西的另一个自我
What you told me about Josie's alter ego
听起来很像漫画书里的故事
sounds straight out of a comic book,
这对我来说  可比看悲观影片熟悉多了
which is way more my genre than film noir.
所以我一直想办法
So I've just been searching for a way
等她醒来之后能帮到她
to help her after she wakes up.
如果她还能醒来的话
If she wakes up.
- 她还没醒  - 她会醒的
- She hasn't yet. - She will.
如果醒不来  我们就去救她回来
And if she doesn't, we'll find a way to go get her.
我们超级小队可不会落下一个人的
Super Squad never leaves a member behind.
我真希望能告诉我我有多抱歉
I wish I could tell her how sorry I am.
我没能注意到
For not seeing it.
我一直忙着自己
For being so wrapped up in myself
都没看到她有多挣扎
that I didn't even notice she was struggling.
我也应该跟你道歉
And I should apologize to you, too.
我利用了你
For using you.
- 没事的啊  - 有事的
- It's okay. - It's not.
我一切顺利的时候
When things are good with me,
我也没在乎你
I don't give you the time of day.
但我一旦出事
But the second that something goes wrong,
我就来找你了
I come running.
我永远不希望你改变
I never want you to stop doing that.
无论游戏怎么说
No matter what any game says.
我也学到了一个东西
I learned something else, too.
除非我相信自己
I can't crack the case
我才能破案
unless I believe in myself.
我不能一直躲在后面当小跟班了
I can't sit back and play the sidekick.
我也该好好站起来了
It's time I step up for real.
像英雄一样  对吧
Like a superhero, you know?
那你要做的超级英雄要叫什么
What's your superhero name gonna be?
还没想好
Work in progress.
不如叫
How about...
安慰者（棉被）吧
the Comforter?
谁说这是真的
* Ooh, who said it's true *
只有你独自一人时
* That the growing only happens *
才能成长
* On your own? *
他们不了解你和我
* They don't know me and you... *
感谢你做的一切
Thank you for everything.
如果不是因为你
We wouldn't have known what we were up against
我们都不知道要面对什么
if it wasn't for you.
抱歉我带走了多利安
I'm sorry to take Dorian away.
但我现在如果我们现在不行动
But I fear if we don't go now,
可能永远也没机会了
we'll never have that chance again.
我以为你这是  回见
I thought this was, uh, see you soon.
而不是再见
Not goodbye.
这游戏本该是一个安全的地方
The game was supposed to be a safe space.
我实实在在地掌控一切的
I was literally in charge of it.
但我还是死了
And yet I still died.
萨尔瓦多学校
The Salvatore School
是我来过最棒的地方
is the most amazing place I have ever been.
也是最危险的地方
And the most dangerous.
我和多利安自己都没做到  我又怎么能把
How can I tell your students to prioritize their health,
自己的心理和身体健康放到第一位考虑
mental and otherwise, when Dorian and I
去教导你的学生们呢
aren't doing that for ourselves?
他今天差点真的死了  里克
He almost died for real, Ric.
虽然他没事
And even though he's fine,
但总会有另一个怪物
there'll always be another monster.
另一个威胁出现
Another threat.
乔西在对抗的  是很危险的东西
What Josie is wrestling with is very dangerous.
我很不想感觉
And I hate that I feel
好像我们抛下了你
like we're abandoning you.
你知道  游戏的重点  就是逃出去
You know the point of the game is to get out.
所以
So...
可能你赢了吧
I guess you won.
没事的
You know, it's okay.
再见了  里克
Bye, Ric.
努力成长
* Grow as we go. *
嘿
Hey.
抱歉
Sorry.
嘿
Hey.
你把这些照片洗出来了吗
You ever develop those photos?
是啊
Uh, yeah.
不过不确定是什么意思
Um... not sure what they mean, though.
是啊
Mmm. Yeah.
你买了车票吗
Did you ever buy that bus ticket?
买了
Yeah.
但没用上
Uh, I didn't use it, though.
所以我还在这里
So here I am,
找兰登
still trying to find Landon.
是啊  但他没走  霍普
Yeah, except he's not gone, Hope.
他只是忙着学会独自飞翔呢
I mean, he's just busy learning how to fly.
没事吧
Is everything okay?
显然有事啊
Uh... apparently not.
我可能只是觉得
I guess I just thought
我很清楚自己的创伤
that I was crystal clear on my damage...
是啊  有时候知道问题的所在
Yeah, well, sometimes knowing what's wrong
并不会让任何事情容易一点
doesn't make things any easier.
如果游戏是想告诉我
What if what the game was trying to teach me
我和兰登之间总是会有障碍呢
is that something will always come between me and Landon?
好像一个什么
Like some impossible choice
- 我得做出的不可能的选择  - 那就选他啊
- that I'm gonna have to make. - Then choose him.
- 就好像我在酒吧说的  - 我选了
- It's like I said in the bar... - I did.
我选了  感觉很好
I did. And it felt good.
感觉很对
It felt right.
但其实是不对的
But it wasn't right.
如果我上了公车
Because if I got onto that bus,
我就走不出游戏了
I wouldn't have gotten out of the game.
直到我没选他  选了别人  我才出来了
I didn't get to leave until I chose someone over him.
这是我学到的东西吗
Was that my lesson?
无论我多喜欢他
That no matter how much I want him,
我和兰登永远成不了
Landon and I are doomed. Hey, hey, hey...
- 这只是个模拟游戏啊 -  是
- it's just a simulation. - Right.
那为什么感觉如此真实呢
Then why does it feel so true?
看来你们全都来了啊
Looks like the gang's all here.
为什么我被关起来了呢
Hmm, why am I locked up, exactly?
你经历了很多
Well, you've been through a lot.
感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
再好不过了
Never better.
我觉得治疗对我很有效
I think the therapy was really good for me.
你充满了黑魔法
You're full of black magic.
我之前太自私了  都没看到
I was too selfish to see it before, but...
但我能感觉到
I can feel it.
这不是你  乔西
This isn't you, Jo.
现在是了
It is now.
慢慢习惯吧
So get used to it.
以后我就要这样了
'Cause this look is here to stay.
乔西  没事的
Josie, it's okay.
我要先让你继续睡着
I'm just gonna put you back to sleep
我们好想办法搞清楚到底怎么回事
until we can figure out what's going on, okay?
好主意啊
Good idea.
别那么看着我  MG
don't look at me like that, MG.
每个超级小队都需要一个超级恶霸呢
Every Super Squad needs a super villain.
（咒语）
Autem.
别想着帮我了  老爸
Stop trying to help me, Dad.
我永远也好不了了
'Cause I've never been better.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）